Guide to the Aldine manuscripts, 1871-1906
Department of Special Collections
Aldine manuscripts,
1871-1906
Special Collections M0095
Sutton, Hames
1 volume
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None.
Provenance
Gift of George S. Parks, 1964.
Scope and Content
Scrapbook containing letters of American writers and artists to Hames Sutton, editor of THE ALDINE, a periodical devoted to the arts (American) and literature covering primarily the 1870s.
Container List
- J. Sutten. sketches. (Page 1, 3, 11, 20, 25, 28)
- George Davis. sketches. (Page 4, 27)
- Oliver W. Holmes. als, 1872 Feb. 20 (Page 9)
- Bayard Taylor. als, 1872 Feb. 20 (Page 10)
- W.C. Bryant. als, 1877 Nov. 5 (Page 17)
- W.C. Bryant. als, 1874 May 29 (Page 18)
- H.W. Longfellow. als, 1874 May 30 (Page 19)
- Dan Beard. sketches (Page 22)
- J.D. Woodward. als, 1873 Dec. 10 (Page 23)
- Granville Perkins. als, 1884 June 7 (Page 23)
- Granville Perkins. sketches, 1884 June 7 (Page 24 and 44 ff)
- Oliver W. Holmes. als, 1874 May 29 (Page 25)
- Paul W. Haynes. als, 1873 Feb. 6 (Page 26)
- John Hay. als, 1871 Mar. 28 (Page 28)
- John Rogers. als, [18--] Sept. 25 (Page 29)
- James R. Randall. poem, 1887 May 5 (Page 32)
- Eliza Greatorex. als, 1873 Mar. 31 (Page 33)
- James McEntis. als, 1879 Jan. 24 (Page 34)
- Arthur Parton. als, 1872 Nov. 16 (Page 39)
- David Neal. als, 1873 Feb. 17 (Page 40)
- David Neal. als, 1873 Jan. 12 (Page 41)
- David Neal. photograph (Page 40)
- William L. Sheppard [?]. als, 1873 Jan. 31 (Page 42)
- Gilber Burling [?]. als, 1873 Jan. 31 (Page 43)
- Thomas Dunn English. als, n.d. (Page 44)
- H. Balling. als, 1873 Feb. 14 (Page 45)
- Whitelaw Reid. als, 1879 Jan. 29 (Page 46)
- Schuyler Colfax. als, 1872 Feb. 10 (Page 47)
- Frank Markward. als, n.d. (Page 48)
- Frank Markward. poem, 1898 Feb. 24 (Page 49)
- James P. Kenyon. als, 1872 Feb. 19 (Page 50)
- A.J. Drexel Biddle. als, n.d. (Page 50)
- William Wintor. als, 1872 Feb. 22 (Page 51)
- J.T. Fields. als, 1872 Feb. 20 (Page 51)
- William Holst. als, 1872 Feb. 19 (Page 52)
- Henry C. Bowen. als, 1872 Feb. 20 (Page 52)
- Lowell by secretary [?]. als, 1872 Feb. 19 (Page 53)
- Eastman Johnson. als, 1872 Feb. 20 (Page 53)
- T. DeWitt Talmage. als, 1872 Feb. 21 (Page 54)
- Edward E. Hale. als, 1872 Feb. 19 (Page 54)
- Samuel F.B. Morse. als, 1872 Feb. 22 (Page 55)
- J.Q. Adams Ward. als, 1872 Feb. 19 (Page 55)
- Ryan Walker. cartoons (Page 56, 62)
- Edmund C. Stedman. als, 1872 Feb. 18 (Page 58)
- Schuyler Colfax. als, 1872 Feb. 26 (Page 58)
- C.A. Dana. als, 1872 Feb. 22 (Page 59)
- R. Shelton MacKenzie. als, 1872 Feb. 22 (Page 59)
- George W. Curtis. als, 1872 Feb. 22 (Page 60)
- R. Shelton MacKenzie. als, 1872 Feb. 19 (Page 60)
- S. R. Clifford. als, 1872 Feb. 18 (Page 61)
- Henry Morford. als, 1876 Jan. 2 (Page 61)
- J.G. Brown. als, 1906 Nov. 5 (Page 66)
- Selma Berg. als, 1873 Oct. 27 (Page 66)
- Henry W. Longfellow. als, 1877 Oct. 28 (Page 68)